**Terms of Use & Privacy Policy**

Last updated Aug 17, 2022  

By using **Fleur** you accept and agree to be bound by [Fleur Terms of Use](https://floret.app/fleur/privacy_terms.html), [Fleur Privacy Policy](https://floret.app/fleur/privacy_terms.html).

**Fleur Terms of Use** Fleur Premium is enabled via an auto-renewing subscription or a lifetime purchase.  
Subscription automatically renews and will be charged for the renewal unless auto-renew is turned off at least 24 hours before the end of the current period.  
Payment will be charged to iTunes Account at confirmation of purchase.  
Auto-renewal may be turned off by the user by going to the user's Account Settings after purchase.  
The duration and price of each subscription is displayed on the purchase screen, and updated at the time of purchase.  
  
**Fleur Privacy Policy** This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.  

**Use of Information**

* We do not store your data in any other services except your own iCloud account and your own devices.
* We do not store any of your personal information in our servers.
* All the data belongs to the user themselves and we do not have any access to it.
* We use Apple SKAdNetwork to measure Facebook advertising performance. No personal data is collected or shared or stored.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.  
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.  
  
**Questions?**  
  
Please contact us at **hello@floret.app** if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.
